tabletitans.com 2018-12-21

# Toonhound Studios Privacy Policy - Table Titans

## Toonhound Studios Privacy Policy

## **Effective September 23, 2013**

Toonhound Studios is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its users.

TableTitans.com provides users with access to free online entertainment, links to our partners and merchandisers, information related to other Toonhound Studios projects, and a way to contact Toonhound Studios with questions or concerns regarding our sites.

### Personal Information Collected

No personal information is collected on this website from users who browse our content.

### Non-Personal Information Collected

TableTitans.com use Google Analytics, a publishing resource that records non-personally identifiable data such as date and time of visit, return and new visits, browser type, pages visited while on this website, where visitors entered the website, the length of their visit, and where went when they left.

We use this data to help us better understand our users needs and to maintain, update, and otherwise make our website better.

Toonhound Studios may share this non-personally identifiable information on a limited bases with our service provider, with third-parties for the purposes of reporting website usage, or to comply with law.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise share this information with third-parties for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

TableTitans.com uses cookies to keep track of users online patterns and preferences. Some of these cookies are form third-party vendors, including Google, for the purpose of advertising. They are used in the following way:

• Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.  
• Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
• Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager (<http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>).  
• Users may also opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

Users have the ability to manage cookies on their computer with controls in their browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

### Other Websites

TableTitans.com contains links to websites not owned by Toonhound Studios. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these or any other websites. Concerned users should review each website’s privacy policy page to learn how that site collects and uses data.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy & Contact

Toonhound Studios privacy policy may be revised at any time. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such changes will be dated and posted as an update to the Privacy Policy page of this website. Users are encouraged to check back regularly to review the current policy in effect.

Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.  

## Submit your own Tales from the Table!

×
